import IJoke from '../../types/joke';

const jokeData: IJoke[] = [
  {
    'id': 1,
    'question': 'Why don’t bartenders ever run out of ice?',
    'answer': 'Because they know how to keep their cool!',
  },
  {
    'id': 2,
    'question': 'A sandwich walks into a bar.',
    'answer': 'The bartender says, “Sorry, we don’t serve food here.”',
  },
  {
    'id': 3,
    'question': 'Why did the bartender break up with their cocktail?',
    'answer': 'It was just too mixed up!',
  },
  {
    'id': 4,
    'question': 'What do you call a bar with great Wi-Fi?',
    'answer': 'A connect-bar!',
  },
  {
    'id': 5,
    'question': 'Why don’t skeletons go to bars?',
    'answer': 'Because they don’t have the guts!',
  },
  {
    'id': 6,
    'question': 'A bartender says, “We don’t serve time travelers here.”',
    'answer': 'A time traveler walks into a bar.',
  },
  {
    'id': 7,
    'question': 'Why did the lemon go to the bar?',
    'answer': 'To find its zest for life!',
  },
  {
    'id': 8,
    'question': 'What did the beer say to the wine?',
    'answer': '“You’re grape, but I’m brewed to perfection!”',
  },
    {
    'id': 9,
    'question': 'Why don’t ghosts drink in bars?',
    'answer': 'They’re afraid they’ll get booed!',
  },
    {
    'id': 10,
    'question': 'A customer asks, “Do you have anything light?”',
    'answer': 'The bartender hands them a candle',
  },
];

export default jokeData;
